bookmyforex.com 2015-03-25

# BookMyForex - Privacy Policy

BookMyForex (BMF) respects your privacy as a visitor to our site [www.bookmyforex.com](https://www.bookmyforex.com/) It is important for you to understand what information we collect about you during your visit and what we do with that information.  Your visit to this Site is subject to this "Privacy Policy" and our Terms of Use, as may be amended from time to time. 

## Information Collection and Use

We will not use information provided through your use of this Site except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

## Active Data Collection

We collect information from our visitors both by asking specific questions on this site   and by permitting you to communicate directly with us via e-mail. Some information that you  submit may be personally identifiable/personal information (that is, information that can   be uniquely identified with you, such as your name, address, e-mail address, phone number,   etc.) and/or sensitive personal information (that is, information which relates to the following   \- password; financial information such as bank account or credit card or debit card or other   payment instrument details; physical, physiological and mental health condition; sexual   orientation, medical records and history; biometric information; any details relating to the   above clasues as provided to us for providing service; and any of the information received under   above clauses by us for processing, stored or processed under lawful contract or otherwise,   provided the same is not avialable in the public domain). We use this information to send you   further information regarding our services.  

## Passive Data Collection

We may collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning  your use of this Site, such as information regarding which of our pages are most often visited.  We may share with or transfer to third parties such non-personally identifiable information for   the purpose of maintaining the Site, responding to direct inquiries or measuring traffic and traffic   trends at this Site. We do not otherwise provide or sell any of this information to third parties.   We do not currently use "cookies" - files written to the visitor's computer that are used by some   Sites for record-keeping or to remember certain information about visitors. We reserve the right   to change our Privacy Policy with respect to our practices regarding the use of cookies and collection   of information from visitors. 

## Use of Information

BookMyForex uses your personal information and sensitive personal information to enhance the operation of this site,  allow you to use all of its features and respond to your requests for information. We may contact you about new  features or services in which it believes you may be interested. 

We may disclose any information we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law,  regulation, legal process or governmental request. 

## Log Files

We may use IP addresses to analyze usage, administer our Site, and gather demographic information for aggregate use. 

## Third Parties and Retention of Information

We may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include data  analysis firms and web hosting companies. Such third parties may be provided with the information  described above. A list of such third parties may be provided under circumstances warranted under   applicable law. Further, we will not retain any personal information or sensitive personal information  for longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it has been collected 

## Transfer and Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information

We may transfer or disclose your sensitive personal information to other third parties provided they  implement the same level of security practices as we do i.e. not below the standards of IS/ISO/IEC 27001.   Such transfer or disclosure shall be for lawful purposes. 

## Choices You Have About How We Use Your Information

We strive to provide you with as many choices and as much control as possible regarding the personal information   you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:  

You may send us an e-mail message at info@bookmyforex.com to request access to, correct or delete any personal information and  sensitive personal information that you have provided to us. 

You may also opt out of the consent so given to us to collect, use, transfer and/or disclose your personal information  and/or sensitive personal information and of receiving marketing messages from us by notifying us at info@bookmyforex.com 

You should review this privacy policy carefully, because if you do not agree with our practices, your ultimate  choice is not to use this site. Remember, by using any part of this Site, you accept and agree to our privacy   practices. If we update this privacy policy, your continued use of this Site (following the posting of the   revised policy) means that you accept and agree to the terms of the revised privacy policy. 

## How We Protect Your Information (Reasonable Security Practices)

We work hard to protect your personal information. We use both technical and procedural methods to maintain the  integrity and security of our databases, including firewalls. We have implemented security standards not lower   than IS/ISO/IEC 27001 to protect your personal information and/or sensitive personal information.  

## Links

This Site may contain links to or from other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the  privacy practices of other websites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information we collect on   this Site. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other websites you link to from our Site or   otherwise visit. 

## Notification of Changes

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will  post the revised policy here. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that  you periodically consult this Privacy Policy. Please note that our rights to use any information collected   will be based on the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is used. 

## What We Do About Children Visiting This Web Site

This Site is not intended for minors. We will not knowingly collect information from Site visitors in   the age group of minors, as per applicable law. 

## Comments and Grievances

We have taken great measures to ensure that your visit to our Site is a satisfying one and that your privacy  is constantly respected. If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy practices,   please contact our grievance officer by e-mail at info@bookmyforex.com or telephone at 09212219191
